# Agustin Bautista

Contact: 206-747-3198 abautist703@gmail.com

Portfolio: www.agustinbautista.com

Profile

Excellent front-end web development skills with an eye for design. Fully competent building full stack web applications with experience using node.js and ruby on rails. Organized, detail-oriented and with international account management experience, I stay on top of deadlines and prioritize work decisively.

Experience

#### Teaching Assistant, General Assembly

Seattle, WA - Jan 2016-present

Regular interaction with 15+ students, guiding instruction on various web development topics, debugging and communicating coding best practices. Provide assistance on several projects built in various languages and frameworks including node.js and ruby on rails

#### Web Development Immersive, General Assembly

Seattle, WA - Sep 2015-Dec 2015

12-week program covers HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, node.js, express.js, PostgreSQL, Ruby on Rails, AngularJS, and other technologies

### Organic Farmer, Jumanji Farm

Sno-Valley and Seattle, WA - May 2014-Dec 2015

Founded and managed small-scale mixed vegetable farm as a participant of Sno-Valley Tilth's Experience Farming Project. Sold organic produce through a CSA subscription service and farmers markets in Seattle.

## Senior Associate, Ogilvy Financial | Ogilvy Public Relations

Beijing and Singapore - Aug 2009-Dec 2012

Supported communications and investor relations programs for various China-based US-listed companies. Responsibilities included account management, planning, strategy, and media outreach

Education

General Assembly; Seattle, WA - web development immersive, 2015 Hamilton College; Clinton, NY – B.A. cum laude, Chinese studies, 2008

Skills

Responsive Web Design | HTML5 | CSS3 | Sass | JavaScript | jQuery | Express.js | Node.js | Ruby on Rails | Bootstrap | PostgreSQL | MongoDB | Git | AngularJS | React | ES2015

References

Brian Hague, General Assembly Web Developer, Instructor — <a href="mailto:brian.hague@ga.co">brian.hague@ga.co</a>
Josh Sera, General Assembly Mobile Developer, Instructor — <a href="mailto:josh.sera@ga.co">josh.sera@ga.co</a>
Annie Ly, General Assembly Education Programs Manager — <a href="mailto:annie.ly@generalassemb.ly">annie.ly@generalassemb.ly</a>